[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", ":", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "But what has there been today that we know for sure in terms of development?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "has", "there", "been", "today", "that", "we", "know", "for", "sure", "in", "terms", "of", "development", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Well, we know that there has been some -- there have been some advances made in the investigation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "know", "that", "there", "has", "been", "some", "--", "there", "have", "been", "some", "advances", "made", "in", "the", "investigation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Do we know what any of this means?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "know", "what", "any", "of", "this", "means", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, potentially it is significant.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "potentially", "it", "is", "significant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Has there -- is there a bit of chaos behind the scenes?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "there", "--", "is", "there", "a", "bit", "of", "chaos", "behind", "the", "scenes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "That's probably what you should be reading into it.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "probably", "what", "you", "should", "be", "reading", "into", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "I'm well, Piers, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "well", ",", "Piers", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "It's -- you're such a cheery individual by nature.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "you", "'re", "such", "a", "cheery", "individual", "by", "nature", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Do you know why they cancelled it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "why", "they", "cancelled", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "CC", "JJ", ":", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Do you know what they have seen or how clear the images are?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "they", "have", "seen", "or", "how", "clear", "the", "images", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Well, I've been briefed, and I understand some of that and other -- and other evidence that is being pursued -- you know, yesterday the FBI asked the general public to submit their own photographs and videotape.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "briefed", ",", "and", "I", "understand", "some", "of", "that", "and", "other", "--", "and", "other", "evidence", "that", "is", "being", "pursued", "--", "you", "know", ",", "yesterday", "the", "FBI", "asked", "the", "general", "public", "to", "submit", "their", "own", "photographs", "and", "videotape", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Why did you go to the marathon and how had your day been until that point?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "go", "to", "the", "marathon", "and", "how", "had", "your", "day", "been", "until", "that", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "It's good to see you tonight, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "good", "to", "see", "you", "tonight", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "What made you do that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I honestly can't tell you where I drew the power from to do that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "honestly", "ca", "n't", "tell", "you", "where", "I", "drew", "the", "power", "from", "to", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "What did you see around you as you went into try and help?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "see", "around", "you", "as", "you", "went", "into", "try", "and", "help", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "I approached an officer first and told her I had had some medical training in the past with mass casualty stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "approached", "an", "officer", "first", "and", "told", "her", "I", "had", "had", "some", "medical", "training", "in", "the", "past", "with", "mass", "casualty", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Have you made any contact with her?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "made", "any", "contact", "with", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "I haven't been able to make any contact with her, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "been", "able", "to", "make", "any", "contact", "with", "her", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "What is it that you were able to say to her by way of comfort in that moment of acute agony for her?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "that", "you", "were", "able", "to", "say", "to", "her", "by", "way", "of", "comfort", "in", "that", "moment", "of", "acute", "agony", "for", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "I got her to look at me, first off.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "her", "to", "look", "at", "me", ",", "first", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gulf of Mexico"]}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Where did you have that?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "have", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "I was actually employed by a couple oil companies working in the Gulf of Mexico on offshore drilling rigs.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "actually", "employed", "by", "a", "couple", "oil", "companies", "working", "in", "the", "Gulf", "of", "Mexico", "on", "offshore", "drilling", "rigs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Did you feel that it was usually helpful of that you had been through that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "that", "it", "was", "usually", "helpful", "of", "that", "you", "had", "been", "through", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "I believe you're currently unemployed, is that right, Tyler?", "question_tokens": ["I", "believe", "you", "'re", "currently", "unemployed", ",", "is", "that", "right", ",", "Tyler", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tyler"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Would you like to do that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "In terms of speculation, where is your head taking you with this investigation?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "speculation", ",", "where", "is", "your", "head", "taking", "you", "with", "this", "investigation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Well, Piers, I keep on going back and forth.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "keep", "on", "going", "back", "and", "forth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Is it all pointing now to the hallmarks of an al Qaeda strike?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "all", "pointing", "now", "to", "the", "hallmarks", "of", "an", "al", "Qaeda", "strike", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "It does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "What do you make of the way the FBI is conducting this so far?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "way", "the", "FBI", "is", "conducting", "this", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Piers, I think it's a very difficult investigation to conduct.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "difficult", "investigation", "to", "conduct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "How would you be playing that if you were the FBI?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "be", "playing", "that", "if", "you", "were", "the", "FBI", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "I think it would depend upon how much other information they had to go along with those pictures.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "would", "depend", "upon", "how", "much", "other", "information", "they", "had", "to", "go", "along", "with", "those", "pictures", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Is your head moving towards al Qaeda, as many others seem to be?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "your", "head", "moving", "towards", "al", "Qaeda", ",", "as", "many", "others", "seem", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "As the -- two of the three people you spoke to just a minute ago were, it is tending toward that.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "the", "--", "two", "of", "the", "three", "people", "you", "spoke", "to", "just", "a", "minute", "ago", "were", ",", "it", "is", "tending", "toward", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Qaeda"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "What do you do about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Well, you defeat a network with a network.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "defeat", "a", "network", "with", "a", "network", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Is this a failure?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "a", "failure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Not necessarily.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "necessarily", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "What is your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "I am disgusted and so disappointed in our Senate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "disgusted", "and", "so", "disappointed", "in", "our", "Senate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "CD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "If the deaths of 20 young children and your sister and five other adults at an elementary school, if that isn't enough to bring in something, what is?", "question_tokens": ["If", "the", "deaths", "of", "20", "young", "children", "and", "your", "sister", "and", "five", "other", "adults", "at", "an", "elementary", "school", ",", "if", "that", "is", "n't", "enough", "to", "bring", "in", "something", ",", "what", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "You know, if they were to lose a loved one to a horrific tragedy like we did, they would feel the same way.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "if", "they", "were", "to", "lose", "a", "loved", "one", "to", "a", "horrific", "tragedy", "like", "we", "did", ",", "they", "would", "feel", "the", "same", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Are you staggered by the reaction of fellow Americans to this?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "staggered", "by", "the", "reaction", "of", "fellow", "Americans", "to", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNPS", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "I'm disgusted with it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "disgusted", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "What do you say to those senators that voted all this stuff down today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "those", "senators", "that", "voted", "all", "this", "stuff", "down", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "That they should be ashamed.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "they", "should", "be", "ashamed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "What do you intend to do next?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "intend", "to", "do", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Keep fighting.", "answer_tokens": ["Keep", "fighting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "What was your reaction that suddenly all these people were being brought to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "that", "suddenly", "all", "these", "people", "were", "being", "brought", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Well, you know, we got very little notice in advance.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "got", "very", "little", "notice", "in", "advance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "In terms of the severity and scale of the injuries, have you in your career ever encountered anything quite like it?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "the", "severity", "and", "scale", "of", "the", "injuries", ",", "have", "you", "in", "your", "career", "ever", "encountered", "anything", "quite", "like", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "So in what we do, we will see people with injuries like this, but what's unique about this, certainly in the civilian population, is the number of patients with such severe injuries.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "in", "what", "we", "do", ",", "we", "will", "see", "people", "with", "injuries", "like", "this", ",", "but", "what", "'s", "unique", "about", "this", ",", "certainly", "in", "the", "civilian", "population", ",", "is", "the", "number", "of", "patients", "with", "such", "severe", "injuries", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "It seems extraordinary that so many were hit and yet so few, in the end, ended up losing their lives?", "question_tokens": ["It", "seems", "extraordinary", "that", "so", "many", "were", "hit", "and", "yet", "so", "few", ",", "in", "the", "end", ",", "ended", "up", "losing", "their", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Yeah, I think this was a very unique situation.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "think", "this", "was", "a", "very", "unique", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130417pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "How hard is it for you, as a human being, to see a five-year-old kid brought in who's been blown up by somebody, by a terrorist?", "question_tokens": ["How", "hard", "is", "it", "for", "you", ",", "as", "a", "human", "being", ",", "to", "see", "a", "five-year-old", "kid", "brought", "in", "who", "'s", "been", "blown", "up", "by", "somebody", ",", "by", "a", "terrorist", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "RP", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "You know, I think it's very difficult for all of us, for all the patients.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "difficult", "for", "all", "of", "us", ",", "for", "all", "the", "patients", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]